const myQuestions = [
    {
        question: 'Which festival does &#127877 represent?',
        answers: {
            a: 'Easter',
            b: 'Christmas',
            c: 'Halloween',
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which event does &#127793 represent?',
        answers: {
            a: 'Earth day',
            b: 'Globe day',
            c: "St Patrick's day",
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which event does &#127941 represent?',
        answers: {
            a: 'Volleyball',
            b: 'Tennis',
            c: 'Olympics',
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which festival does &#127875 represent?',
        answers: {
            a: 'Halloween',
            b: 'New Years Eve',
            c: 'Independence Day',
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which festival does &#9899 represent?',
        answers: {
            a: 'Hanukkah',
            b: 'Black friday',
            c: 'Chinese New year',
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which event does &#128214 represent?',
        answers: {
            a: 'World Book day',
            b: 'Graduation',
            c: "Women's day",
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which event does &#128105 represent?',
        answers: {
            a: 'Mothers day',
            b: 'Fathers day',
            c: "Children's day",
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which event does &#128009 represent?',
        answers: {
            a: 'Chinese New Year',
            b: 'New Year',
            c: 'Emoji day',
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which event does &#9752 represent?',
        answers: {
            a: 'Earth day',
            b: "St Patrick's day",
            c: 'Emoji day',
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which event does &#10084 represent?',
        answers: {
            a: 'Thanks Giving',
            b: 'Veterans day',
            c: 'Valentines day',
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c',
    },
];
